Tomasz Żuber

Links & Contact

tomaszzportfolio.vercel.app

in/tomasz-zuber95

tomaszz95

tzuber95@gmail.com

remote / willing to relocate

Education

2014 - 2019
Mining Surveying
Silesian University of Technology
Master's Degree

Work Experience

2021 - Currently Land Surveyor Specialist Asgeodezja Sp. z o. o. Mikolów

2019 - 2021 Land Surveyor Land surveying services, Mikolów

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Problem solving
- Effective communication
- Good time management
- Attention to details
- Learning from mistakes
- Responsibility

Languages

- Polish native
- English B2

Interests

- Modern technologies
- Hiking
- Bushcraft
- Piano playing

About me

I am an aspiring frontend junior developer who is disciplined, ambitious, hard-working, and ready to continuously expand my programming knowledge and further develop my skills. I have been learning programming for more than two years and have reached the point where my current goal is to get my first position as a frontend developer. My technological stack and skills enable me to apply for most positions at the 'junior' or 'intern' level – unfortunately I only lack commercial experience. My goal for the future is to evolve into a full-stack developer by enhancing my skills in database maintenance and backend development.

Projects

Portfolio – a simple portfolio page with more information about me

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/mainsite

Live: https://tomaszzportfolio.vercel.app

This is a fully functional and responsive portfolio website, with more information about me, the projects I have created, the technologies I use and ways to contact me. Additionally, the website features a form that allows you to send me a message directly.

Stack: NextJS, React, Typescript, Tailwind, Git/Github, RWD, SEO, Accessibility.

Netflix clone – fully responsive website, which is an advanced clone of the popular streaming service Netflix, with many of its features

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/Netflixclone Live: https://nerflixcloneen.vercel.app

A website that is a 'clone of Netflix' – it is fully responsive, with best SEO and accessibility practices and with many features from the original streaming site. The application includes numerous sub-pages, ranging from the main view to the registration and login processes, profile selection and editing, as well as the main pages for series, movies, individual sub-pages, and search pages. This is my most significant and advanced project to date – the app is built with approximately 250 components and encompasses around 30 different subpages, including the dynamic ones.

Stack: NextJS, React, Typescript, Firebase, CSS, Git/Github, RWD, SEO, Accessibility.

Gradebook – an online app for students and teachers

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/gradebook

Live: https://gradebookk.vercel.app

An application that partially mimics the operation of an electronic gradebook. The appenables you to check your timetable, grades, statistics related to the grades, and comparisons with other students/classes. As a teacher, you can add news and assign grades to individual students. It combines frontend with backend and retrieving data from databases.

Stack: NextJS, React, Typescript, Firebase, MongoDB, CSS, Git/Github, SEO, Accessibility.

Toolkit – a website with several apps: Todo List, Notes, Calculator, Financial management, Weather App

Github: https://github.com/tomaszz95/toolkit

Live: https://toolkiit.netlify.app

A website with the most popular frontend projects written in React, using React Redux and React Router, as well as Local Storage. The page is fully responsive.

Stack: React, React Redux, CSS, Git/Github, RWD, SEO, Accessibility.

Tech Skills / Stack

- NextJS
- React Redux
- Tailwind
- CSS/SCSS
- · Git/Github
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB

- React
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- HTML
- RWD, SEO
- Tailwind
- Firebase

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).